<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

<channel>

<language>en-us</language>
<title>Jordan's RSS Blog</title>
<link>https://jordiisepic.me</link>
<description>Random blog, not much else.</description>
<author>jordiisepic@jordiisepic.me</author>

<item>
 <title>Awesome sauce</title>
 <link>https://jordiisepic.me</link>
 <description>Literally awesomeness.</description>
 <pubDate>Sat, 3 Dec 2020 11:52:00 -0500</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
 <title>Why I keep redesigning my site (and why I'm going to stop)</title>
 <link>https://jordiisepic.me</link>
 <description>If you haven't noticed, I keep redesigning my site which is probably irritating noticing the fact that there's a lack of consistancy with my brand. I'm sorry about that, but I genuinely don't know why I keep doing it. I just do it when I was bored, but I plan to stop now because I noticed that it's hurting my brand and I want to be consistant with how I brand myself on the internet.</description>
 <pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2020 11:08:00 -0500</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
 <title>Quitting Twitter - My side</title>
 <link>https://jordiisepic.me</link>
 <description>I've decided to quit Twitter and just limit internet usage overall. Realized a while ago that it's been affecting my social status and overall health. I feel that this will improve myself as a person overall. This will also give me a chance to work on my schoolwork that I'm severly behind on. I feel I've rambled on enough about this, not anything too interesting. I'm sure you've heard this from others many times.</description>
 <pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 23:40:00 -0500</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
 <title>Why I think Reddit isn't a bad platform overall</title>
 <link>https://jordiisepic.me</link>
 <description>I'm sure we've seen all the memes surrounding the popular social platform Reddit. Most of them mocking the platform or moderators of said platform, but honestly the platform isn't awful. If you find what communities you're into, (for me: r/ps2, r/wiiu, r/psp) then you have all the content you care for right there. No giant cesspools of garbage (usually).</description>
 <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 23:21:00 -0500</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
 <title>RSS blog debut</title>
 <link>https://jordiisepic.me</link>
 <description>Hello, my RSS blog will mostly consist of random thoughts and changes in my life. I doubt I'll even do weekly posts, but we'll see. Who knows what'll be on here?</description>
 <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 23:16:00 -0500</pubDate>
</item>

</channel>

</rss> 